My name is Utuofon David Udo.
I am a student of the University of Calabar.
I have difficulty in walking because I sustained an accident.
I had a fracture on my ankle when I was driving to school.
Ok, you are a student of where?
The University of Calabar.
You mean you are still an undergraduate?
Yes.
When you are healed now, you will double your hair.
When you see them today - undergraduates - they begin to live as if they are working-class people.
If you now become working class, what will you put on?
This is the problem we are facing today.
Time for everything.
Can we say that our parents, after giving us the school fees,
they should give us extra money to do our hair?
This is the time to talk to her.
After healing now, you can't talk to her.
That is when you will see this.
Did you listen to me?
Yes.
You cannot read with this; it's not possible.
Promise - you have to cut your coat according to your size.
Yes.
What are you looking for? You are a beautiful girl already.
But with this one now, you look ugly.
Remove it, you will see your beauty, okay?
Yes.
Thank you. I think God wants me to talk to you, that is why you have this challenge.
Healing In Jesus' Name
Come on! Remove it!
As Prophet T.B. Joshua begins to offer prayer to Miss Udo, he instructs one of the evangelists,
to remove the ankle brace on her leg.
This is operation.
Yes, I have had three surgeries - two in Nigeria, one in India.
And you still carry this one?
You have to make God proud.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for the complete healing
of Miss Udo's ankle on which she had had three surgeries.
He tells her to rise up on her feet.
Look here.
Come on.
Healed In Jesus' name
Thank You, Jesus! I'm free!
Thank You, Jesus! My sister can walk!
The power of God has touched her life and she is able to walk again without the ankle brace.
Halleluyah!
TESTIMONY TIME
We want the lady to come forward and share her wonderful testimony to the glory of God.
Yes, we can see the glory of God radiating in the life of the sister.
Wow! To God be the glory!
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Utotofon David. I am a student of the University of Calabar.
What brought me to The SCOAN was the problem of difficulty in walking.
I sustained a fracture of the tibia bone and left bone in a car accident in 2014 - 4th July to be precise.
I was in a car with my friend; we were driving, coming back from school.
And then we hit the biggest roundabout in Calabar and we jumped over to the other side of the road.
When we came out of the car, I discovered that I couldn't walk.
I tried to take 2 or 3 steps; I saw my leg was already swelling up and I could not walk.
So passersby took us in and took us to the hospital.
They sent for my mother. When she came, she was scared of surgery.
When she heard the fact that I was supposed to undergo an operation, she was afraid.
So she took me out from the hospital; and then she took me home.
She took me to a traditional bonesetter to try to fix my leg.
After some couple of weeks, there was still no solution and so we decided to go for the operation
that she had opted out initially.
When we went to the hospital, the doctor said, it was a little bit too late for the bone situation.
But he was still going to do the surgery. Then he operated on me the first time.
I was still having pains. There was no solution.
I went to another hospital, still in Abuja, Nigeria, and had another surgery.
There was still no solution.
So she took me to a hospital outside Nigeria; that is, in India.
They operated on me the third time, and we stayed there for three months,
so they could follow up on their physical therapies and everything.
But still there was no solution. So I got back home.
I have been going to rehabilitation centers, different places just to get a solution
but there was no solution.
It affected me in several ways. I couldn't take a shower on my own.
My siblings were the ones doing these things for me.
When they were back to school, it was my mother who would be doing those things for me.
It affected me so much in school that I had to write to my department
that they should please pardon me to write exams.
I was not even able to attend 70% of the lecture time
that is recommended for students to attend before writing exams.
They asked me to suspend my schooling until I would be totally healed.
But I could not because that was the only thing I could hold onto.
I didn't really want to be depressed due to doing nothing so they accepted it; they granted my request.
So I only went there to write exams or for some seminars.
I couldn't attend day-to-day lectures throughout this period when I was having this problem.
Tell us, why were you not able to attend the lectures? Why?
Because I couldn't walk to the lecture halls or run around as a student in school or for anything.
I was really in pains and my legs would be swelling up all the time so I could not make it.
I started watching Emmanuel TV where we were lodging for the very last surgery I had to undergo.
So I said to my mother that, I have been watching this TV,
and I have seen what the man of God has been doing in people's lives.
We had gone virtually everywhere. She had done everything as a mother
to make sure that I was ok but everything was still the same.
That I would like to come here to Lagos, and come to The SCOAN
so that I can have my permanent solution.
And so she asked how I was going to come here,
because during that time, she had been following me to all the hospitals for months;
she had been staying away from her place of work and she had big problems.
She was queried or something that she had stayed away from work for so long, for some months.
So she said she could not come with me anymore
because she was already having problems at her place of work.
How was I going to come to The SCOAN?
So she called her sister and explained the situation.
So her sister send her son that could bring me to Lagos.
That was how we came to The SCOAN.
So tell us - what happened on that day?
When I came to The SCOAN last week, before the man of God even prayed for me,
he did something that only a loving father would do to his children.
He advised me.
Miss Ututofon David & Family
Healing Testimony
He corrected me on some things and I promised him I was going to keep to his advice.
And that is why I'm looking like this today.
Miss Ututofon David & Family
Healing Testimony
Ok, tell us once again. What was the correction he gave to you?
He said I should cut my coat according to my size as a student.
That I should remove the wig that was on my hair and I should just live as a student.
Yes, to live the life of Christ so that you can be able to assimilate as a student
and live in the righteous way of the Lord.
So now, how has that advice improved your life?
I discovered that I didn't even need them anymore. I mean I have my own hair.
I didn't need to attach anything to it any more. So, the advice - it's really good.
And I can also share it to my friends.
Wow, to God be the glory. Put your hands together beautifully for Jesus!
We thank God Almighty that you have taken to that advice
and we can really see in you the glory of God.
Even looking at you now, one can see the glory of God
and the beauty of God in your life as you are looking naturally as God has created you.
Continue with your testimony.
So on that day when the man of God came to you, what happened?
I remember when I was watching Emmanuel TV in April on the resurrection morning -
that was on a Sunday - I had a dream. In that dream, I saw myself.
I was still very sick and couldn't walk and so my mother here and my elder sister,
I saw them carrying me. That I should come as there was somebody that was healing people.
That I had been in that situation for too long. That I should come.
And so they carried me - one by the left shoulder and one by the right shoulder.
They took me to a particular room and said, "Just wait, be patient, be of good courage,
it will be your turn". And so I was waiting; I was laying on a mat.
Suddenly, I heard my name. I said, "Mummy, they are calling me". She said, "Yes".
And so they took me. When I reached the hall, it was Prophet T.B. Joshua who was there.
He stood at a distance from me and just said to me, "Be healed!"
And then right from that moment when he said, "Be healed",
I experienced a sensation from my waist down, it was a shocking sensation.
That was the sensation that woke me up to reality.
So that was a spiritual manifestation of your healing, your miracle that happened.
So now tell us - what happened on that day when you now physically met
the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua?
When I woke up, I told my mother about it when she came back from church.
She told me that though she didn't believe in dreams but what she could tell me as a mother was
that though my faith could not carry what I had just seen in the dream, her suggestion would be that
I should come to The SCOAN so that I could meet with the man of God,
so that my healing could come to reality since my faith could not take me.
When I came to Tthe SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me.
As soon as he prayed for me, he told me to walk and I started walking to the glory of God.
Wow! Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus Christ!
So you mean, as the man of God came to you and prayed for you
and told you to stand up and walk, you found herself walking.
What you could not do before, you found yourself doing it, to the glory of God,
Yes. Even that day when I came, I was being supported by my brother there.
I was still limping, obviously. But as soon as he told me to walk, I started walking.
And right now, I can even walk much more better.
Wow. Shall we put our hands together once again for Jesus!
Wow. To God be the glory. We thank God Almighty for what He has done in your life.
Can you demonstrate to us what you can do now, what you could not do before but now you can do,
after the prayer of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua in your life.
Before, I couldn't walk without limping. If I walked, it would be so obvious that I was limping.
But now, I can walk very well, and you wouldn't know anything. I give God the glory.
Thank You, Jesus!
Wow. To God be the glory.
On that day, we saw you with an ankle brace.
Are you still using the ankle brace?
No, I don't need the ankle brace anymore.
You don't need it anymore. Now you can do the things you could not do before,
to the glory of God. Wow, to God be the glory.
We thank God Almighty for His miracle in your life and as you can see on the screen,
we can see the day when the man of God prayed for her and God Almighty healed her
from the problem she was having, to the glory of God.
We can even see now that you are putting on shoes. Can we see?
Could you do all this before? Could you put on shoes like this and walk around?
No I couldn't.
But now you can do them to the glory of God which shows the mightiness of God in your life.
To God be the glory.
What advice do you have for people listening to you
because many people are also in the same condition that you were in before,
and they don't know how to go about it. What advice do you have for them?
My advice to people that are in this situation, especially to the young people, is
that after trying everything you think you can do -
I mean God's wisdom starts from where human knowledge stops.
So I advise every young person to run to God - to come to The SCOAN if you can.
But if you can't, watch Emmanuel TV, listen to the man of God and then do what he says you should do.
And then you will have your healing miracle or whatever you expect from God.
Miss Ututofon David & Family
Healing Testimony
The woman standing beside me is my mother and the man standing beside me is my brother.
My mother's sister's son - he is my brother.
Ok. Can we just hear a few words from your mother.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Brethren, I want to thank God. I am not going to narrate the whole story again.
The young beautiful angel standing beside me is my second daughter from a family of five.
You know what it means for a young girl to have an accident - since 2014.
All I am saying now is that God has done it for me, in the name of Jesus.
God has done it so that I no longer have to carry her, carry water to her, do everything for her.
I mean, this accident did a lot of things to me - even the hypertension that I am having now,
at my place of work, everything.
It was because of the accident, running here and there.
I can remember one day that I was going to give a letter to the HOD in the University of Calabar.
As I was going, the BP started going up. I asked the driver to stop.
He said, "Madam, what happened?" I said, "I can't continue on this journey".
He asked, "Why?" I said, "Please stop. Where I am going to is far but here is nearer.
Let me just go back to the house".
I got off, after I had payed the money.
It went on like that. Till even when we travelled.
So, finally today - as I said, I am not going to narrate any story,
but all I'm saying is that God has done it for me.
And I want to thank God for this church, The SCOAN and the prophet, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God is using him and God should keep him so that he will continue this work.
I cannot reward him, but I know that our Heavenly Father is a Rewarder
and He says in His Word that He will reward those who seek diligently for Him.
And I know that He will reward him, in Jesus' name.
We thank God Almighty for the glorious testimony that has been shared by your daughter.
Shall we put our hands together once again for Jesus Christ!
We thank God Almighty, sister, for what the Lord has done in your life.
We just want to enjoin and employ you that now that you have been healed and set free,
you should go and make God's Word the standard for your life
and let your way be channelled by the Word of God.
Remember, the healing that you have received is not an end in itself
but a means to an end which is the salvation of your soul.
Amen.
TT: Monica Asefa 21/07/18
RV: Mel Flowers 02/08/2018